You might think of those projects that those people as kind of like slightly disreputable or kind of
not to be trusted, or you know kind of like chances, basically, because that's what they are
But
Heads I win, tails you lose. If the people who kick projects off
Realize that they can adopt a strategy where if the project is successful, they can be around and take the credit for it and kind of get value out of the project.
And if the project isn't successful, there can be nowhere near it and claim to not have any knowledge of it
And
Basically say, oh, it's nothing to do with me. I don't know how that project happened.
Then if they can adopt that strategy and they realize they can adopt that strategy
Then
They're much more tempted to kick off more projects.
And again, this sounds like kind of quite a disreputable thing.